{"description":"A set of questions to test the software with","name":"Airdrop Pilot","questions":[{"question":"203. Loading the GPS keys improves FFS performance.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"1C -17A -1 Para : 2-580(N)","responses":["True","False"]},{"question":"204. Maximum troop door opening airspeed is _____. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"1C -17A -1 Fig : 5 -6","responses":["280 KCAS\/Mach 0.62","350 KCAS\/Mach 0.825","310 KCAS\/Mach 0.74","250 KCAS\/Mach 0.62"]},{"question":"205. Static line personnel airdrops over the ramp are _____ ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"1C -17A -1 Para : 5 -73","responses":["Authorized for specifically designated Air Force units.","Prohibited.","Authorized for specifically designated Navy units.","Authorized only when done in conjunction with boat drops. "]},{"question":"206. If the crosstrack error abeam the CARP\/HARP is predicted to be greater than ____ at any time during usable DZ time, the CAWS annunciates \"AUTO DROP,\" and the AUTO DROP annunciator on the instrument panel illuminates. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"1C -17A -1 -2 Para : 1 -2226","responses":["100 yards","250 yards","300 yards","500 yards "]},{"question":"207. Formation takeoff minimums are no lower than a ____ ceiling and _____ mile(s) visibility. Formation landing minimums are ____. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V3 Para : 18.3.1 & 18.3.2","responses":["500 ft; 1 mile; 300 ft ceiling and u00be mile visibility","600 ft; 2 miles; 500 ft ceiling and 2 miles visibility","300 ft; 3\/4 mile; 600 ft ceiling and 2 miles visibility","200 ft 1\/2 mile; published minimums for the airport "]},{"question":"208. Lead will announce unplanned airspeed changes of _____ knots or more. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V 3 Para: 18.10.4.3","responses":["10","15","20","All airspeed changes must be announced "]},{"question":"209. (Formation Holding Pattern, Holding Pattern in Lieu of Procedure Turn, or Procedure Turn Pattern) During formation recoveries lead ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V 3 Para: 18.11.11.1","responses":["Will enter a minimum of 1,000 feet above procedure turn or GCA pickup altitude","Will not enter from the quadrant requiring a turn to the non- maneuvering side.","Request 2 minute holding legs with more than 3 aircraft in formation","All of the above "]},{"question":"210. Offset PIs are computed from the surveyed center PI. When used, a _____ yard left\/right offset will be used for 3-ship operations and a _____ yard left\/right offset will be used for 2-ship operations. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI 13 -217 Para: 2.5.7.1","responses":["250; 125","500; 250","500; 125","250; 75 "]},{"question":"211. For smaller formations or single-ship operations, the most desirable shape for a DZ is circular. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 Para : 7.3.1.1","responses":["True","False "]},{"question":"212. For jumpmaster -directed airdrops, the PF must establish drop altitude and airspeed early (normally _____ minutes prior to green light). At approximately until _____ scheduled drop time, the loadmaster permits the jumpmaster to begin spotting procedures. At the _____ minute warning on the PFD, the PM turns on the green light to indicate clearance for the jumpmaster to determine the exact exit point. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 Para : 7.9.3","responses":["2; 2; 1","5; 3; 1","3; 3; 2","5; 2; 1 "]},{"question":"213. (Formation En Route Altitude Changes) For climbs and descents greater than 2,000 feet, use _____ FPM (or previous rate if lower). For 2,000 feet or less, use _____ FPM (or previous rate if lower). ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C17 Table 8. 4","responses":["2000; 1000","1000; 1000","2000; 1500","1000; 500"]},{"question":"214. The minimum formation takeoff interval is _____ seconds. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C17 Para : 8.8.4.1","responses":["20","30","40","60 "]},{"question":"215. For visual-in-trail formation slowdowns, the desired spacing is _____ feet between element leads (_____ feet between all aircraft). ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFTT P 3-3.C17 Fig: 8.30","responses":["12000; 4000","6000; 2000","12000; 2000","6000; 4000 "]},{"question":"216. (Visual Formation Airdrop) For drift angles of _____ degree(s), wingmen adjust their lateral formation position to maintain the same relative ground track as the element lead over the DZ, avoiding wake turbulence from the preceding aircraft. ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C17 Para : 8.11 .5.1.1","responses":["4 and greater","1","2","3"]},{"question":"217. (Personnel Formation Airdrop Escape) If required to move back to en route crosstrack, delay post drop maneuvering to en route visual or SKE XTRK position until end of usable DZ (MC Red Light) and \"load clear.\" ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C17 Para : 8.11 .7.2","responses":["True","False"]},{"question":"218. The Quick Drop Checklist may be used for: ","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"1C -17A -1 -4 Para : 2 -98","responses":["A subsequent static line personnel airdrop when all troop doors are closed between passes","A subsequent heavy equipment airdrop pass","A subsequent CDS airdrop when the cargo door and ramp remain open between passes","All of the above"]},{"question":"220. During the airdrop slowdown checklist, the SED thrust rating is selected to MAX if:","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"1C -17A -1 -4 Para: 2 -119 step 2","responses":["Flying in a wing position","Selecting 3\/4 or FULL flaps","Dropping heavy equipment platforms","Both B and C"]},{"question":"219. Airdrop with _____ selected on the MCD's NAV SENSORS-CONTROL PAGE will cause numerous UNABLE RNP messages to annunciate because of aircraft navigational software errors.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"1C-17A-1-4 Para: 2-118 step 8c(N)","responses":["MGPS","CGPS","SKE ZM","RADIO"]}]}
